<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Planet Builder</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_0_class">O</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_1_class">B</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_2_class">A</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_3_class">F</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_4_class">G</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_5_class">K</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_6_class">M</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_0_name">Blue</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_1_name">Blue-White</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_2_name">White</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_3_name">Yellow-White</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_4_name">Yellow</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_5_name">Yellow-Orange</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_6_name">Red</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_0_min_temp">30000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_1_min_temp">10000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_2_min_temp">7500</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_3_min_temp">6000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_4_min_temp">5000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_5_min_temp">3500</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_6_min_temp">0</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_0_max_temp">60000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_1_max_temp">30000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_2_max_temp">10000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_3_max_temp">7500</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_4_max_temp">6000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_5_max_temp">5000</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_6_max_temp">3500</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_0_min_desc">O-type stars are very hot and extremely luminous, with most of their radiated output in the ultraviolet range. These are the rarest of all main-sequence stars. About 1 in 3,000,000 (0.00003%) of the main-sequence stars in the solar neighborhood are O-type stars. Some of the most massive stars lie within this spectral class. O-type stars frequently have complicated surroundings that make measurement of their spectra difficult. The radiation from O5 stars is so intense that it can ionize hydrogen over a volume of space 1000 light years across. One example is the luminous H II region surrounding star cluster M16. O-Type stars are very massive and evolve more rapidly than low-mass stars because they develop the necessary central pressures and temperatures for hydrogen fusion sooner. Because of their early development, the O-Type stars are already luminous in the huge hydrogen and helium clouds in which lower mass stars are forming. They light the stellar nurseries with ultraviolet light and cause the clouds to glow in some of the dramatic nebulae associated with the H II regions.</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_1_min_desc">B-type stars are very luminous and blue. Their spectra have neutral helium, which are most prominent at the B2 subclass, and moderate hydrogen lines. As O- and B-type stars are so energetic, they only live for a relatively short time. Thus, due to the low probability of kinematic interaction during their lifetime, they are unable to stray far from the area in which they formed, apart from runaway stars. These stars tend to be found in their originating OB associations, which are associated with giant molecular clouds. The Orion OB1 association occupies a large portion of a spiral arm of the Milky Way and contains many of the brighter stars of the constellation Orion. About 1 in 800 (0.125%) of the main-sequence stars in the solar neighborhood are B-type main-sequence objects.</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_2_min_desc">A-type stars are among the more common naked eye stars, and are white or bluish-white. They have strong hydrogen lines, at a maximum by A0, and also lines of ionized metals (Fe II, Mg II, Si II) at a maximum at A5. The presence of Ca II lines is notably strengthening by this point. About 1 in 160 (0.625%) of the main-sequence stars in the solar neighborhood are A-type stars.</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_3_min_desc">F-type stars have strengthening H and K lines of Ca II. Neutral metals (Fe I, Cr I) beginning to gain on ionized metal lines by late F. Their spectra are characterized by the weaker hydrogen lines and ionized metals. Their color is white. About 1 in 33 (3.03%) of the main-sequence stars in the solar neighborhood are F-type stars.</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_4_min_desc">G-type stars, including the Sun[11] have prominent H and K lines of Ca II, which are most pronounced at G2. They have even weaker hydrogen lines than F, but along with the ionized metals, they have neutral metals. There is a prominent spike in the G band of CH molecules. Class G main-sequence stars make up about 7.5%, nearly one in thirteen, of the main-sequence stars in the solar neighborhood. G is host to the "Yellow Evolutionary Void". Supergiant stars often swing between O or B (blue) and K or M (red). While they do this, they do not stay for long in the yellow supergiant G classification as this is an extremely unstable place for a supergiant to be.</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_5_min_desc">K-type stars are orangish stars that are slightly cooler than the Sun. They make up about 12%, nearly one in eight, of the main-sequence stars in the solar neighborhood.[nb 3][9] There are also giant K-type stars, which range from hypergiants like RW Cephei, to giants and supergiants, such as Arcturus, whereas orange dwarfs, like Alpha Centauri B, are main-sequence stars. They have extremely weak hydrogen lines, if they are present at all, and mostly neutral metals (Mn I, Fe I, Si I). By late K, molecular bands of titanium oxide become present. There is a suggestion that K Spectrum stars may potentially increase the chances of life developing on orbiting planets that are within the habitable zone</string>
    <string name="stellar_type_6_min_desc">Class M stars are by far the most common. About 76% of the main-sequence stars in the solar neighborhood are class M stars.[nb 3][nb 4][9] However, class M main-sequence stars (red dwarfs) have such low luminosities that none are bright enough to be seen with the unaided eye, unless under exceptional conditions. The brightest known M-class main-sequence star, M0V Lacaille 8760, with magnitude 6.6 (the limiting magnitude for typical naked-eye visibility under good conditions is typically quoted as 6.5) and it is extremely unlikely that any brighter examples will be found. Although most class M stars are red dwarfs, most giants and some supergiants such as VY Canis Majoris, Antares and Betelgeuse are also class M. Furthermore, the hotter brown dwarfs are late class M. This is usually in the range of M6.5 to M9.5. The spectrum of a class M star contains lines from oxide molecules, especially TiO, in the visible and all neutral metals, but absorption lines of hydrogen are usually absent. TiO bands can be strong in class M stars, usually dominating their visible spectrum by about M5. vanadium(II) oxide bands become present by late M.</string>
</resources>
